Welcome your customer.
Singer and actor.
Oh my God.
Welcome your customer.
Hey, In Guk!
[Seo In Guk - Singer and Actor]
Hey, we're so busy.
Welcome your customer.
Where can I sit?
- It's Seo In Guk!
- Are you here for dinner?
- Seo In Guk!
- Yes?
Wow, he's so handsome.
Is it Seo In Guk?
Yeah, it's Seo In Guk.
He really is handsome.
- Hey, In Guk.
- Yeah?
- We're so busy right now.
- Yeah.
Can you help us clean up?
- But I'm a customer.
- Please, just this once.
- I even got you a gift.
- Oh well.
How can I help?
We need to clear these first.
[The Aftermath of the Dinner Rush]
- Everything.
- How do I clear them?
- Come here.
- Are you serious?
Yeah, come here.
- Come here.
- Okay.
[Is This For Real?]
Hello!
- Hello.
We've got a new helper.
Oh, egg.
[Communication Error!]
Plain rice.
Okay, put on your gloves.
Okay.
- There we go.
- Okay.
Can you clear all those tables?
Hello, Francine!
Oh, hi! How are you?
- Hello, nice to see you again!
- How have you been?
- Hi.
- When did you get here?
- How did you...
- Our new server.
Oh, thank you!
New server? Oh, thank you.
[The Brothers]
[New Part-Timer?]
Where do I need to clean...
[Starts Anyway...]
[I'm a Customer...]
Tables 3, 1.
Kare-kare, palabok,
sinigang, inasal, gising-gising.
Wow, they're swamped.
[Accepts His Fate...]
Wow, no time to even say hi.
You guys are super busy!
It's my first day as well.
- Oh, today is your first day?
- Yeah.
- Hi.
[Plates Piling Up]
[All Clean!]
- Ji!
- Yeah?
Is there a cloth?
To wipe the table.
[Who is he?]
Give me a sec, I need to find it.
Hi.
Hello.
Okay, I'll make one for you.
[Working Non-Stop!]
Whoa, they're busy!
Ji!
Ji.
Ah, someone, this guy is calling.
A guy in a black hat.
- Black hat? Okay.
- Yeah.
- Here's your cloth.
- Thanks.
Chef said he's asking for you.
- This guy.
- How can I help you?
Is my food coming?
One moment, please.
I got hired all of a sudden.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, go ahead.
- We ordered Coke Zero, but...
- Not out yet?
- Yeah.
- How rude.
- I'll bring it right away.
- Thank you.
- I just spoke with Seo In Guk!
- Awesome.
Sorry, where is Zero Coke?
- Coke Zero?
- Yeah, Coke Zero.
I am not sure.
Okay.
Ah, In Guk, right here.
- Oh, it's here?
- Who should I give it to?
Here, here.
- Is this the right one?
- Yes.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
[One After Another]
Oh, hello!
Table for three?
Please have a seat here.
Oh, I'll wipe the table for you.
You know what? I came here as a customer.
For real.
Oh yeah, that's a customer's outfit.
Right? I'm not wearing the uniform.
[For the Nth Time]
[He's a Customer, Not a Server]
- You can sit here.
- Okay, thank you.
I'll sit here.
[Now Enjoying His Fate]
If you don't mind snacking before the meal,
I can bring some over.
- Yes!
- Yes, thank you!
Water and a napkin, please.
- Water and a napkin.
- Yes.
I'll get you enough napkins.
- You ordered inasal, right?
- And Coke Zero.
- Do you want some garlic rice?
- Yes.
[Thanks to In Guk]
[The Team's Back In Order]
- That's delicious! It's sweet.
- Thank you.
- For your desserts.
- Wow, look at this.
[Waiting Becomes Enjoyable with In Guk]
Nice.
- Did you get your Coke Zero?
- Yes!
That's great.
Happy birthday!
- Here's your napkin.
- Thank you so much!
- We're celebrating his birthday today.
- It's his birthday.
- Today?
- Yes!
Yesterday was my birthday.
- Wow!
- Really?
- Can you sing a song?
- Yeah. Your name?
- Paolo.
- Paolo?
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, my friend Paolo ♪
- Thank you.
- ♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
So nice!
- Have a happy birthday, Paolo!
- Cheers!
- Happy birthday, Paolo!
- Happy birthday!
I think things are going back to normal.
[Server Mode Off, Customer Mode On]
He's going to have his meal now.
Oh, he is finally going to have it.
What's funny is...
I went in there, put on my gloves,
and rolled up my sleeves,
then everyone in there
just naturally put me to work.
I will just have to clean up everything.
Is that okay?
Ah, this guy calling.
A guy in a black hat.
- Black hat? Okay.
- Yeah.
That's not how Francine looked
when she sang "My Love" with me.
She must be so tired.
Oh, here you are. What do you want?
- Can I order?
- Yeah.
Palabok, inasal, kare-kare, and garlic rice.
Okay. How about your drinks?
- Coke Zero.
- Alright.
Chef?
- Can you boil noodles again, please?
- Yeah.
Hot, hot, hot.
Beautiful.
Two palaboks.
This is your palabok.
- Here's your palabok.
- Ah, okay.
How is it?
Is it good?
It's savory.
I love the shrimp aroma.
It tastes familiar, yet unfamiliar.
You're right.
One, two, three, four.
Kare-kare!
Kare-kare.
- Here you go, In Guk.
- Thank you.
Sure.
Why is this so good?
[Kare-kare Keeping His Spoon Busy]
It's so delicious!
Where's our other server?
He's gone.
No, he ate.
Oh, he's eating!
Why?
He's a server!
Ji, inasal.
Oh, okay.
- Here it is.
- Oh, thank you.
I'm sorry for the wait.
- Oh my gosh, I'm satisfied already.
- I can tell Mom's falling for him.
I got butterflies too. He's so handsome.
It's like a fairy showed up.
[She's a Big Fan of Ji]
[Super In Love with Ji]
[Switched to VIP Seat]
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
Got everything but the garlic rice?
[A Dream Come True!]
You're like a young girl again, Mom!
- She is a girl.
- Right.
You're probably his biggest fan here.
That's right.
[After the Chaos...]
[Finally Getting Some Breather]
We don't have any new orders anymore?
No more. They're just finishing up.
That's the best news ever!
- Things are slowing down now?
- Yeah.
How was the taste?
It was good!
This is so tasty.
- Kare-kare?
- Yeah.
- You know what's important?
- What?
I didn't get to try it.
Nothing? Not even one dish?
I tried one chicken leg.
Oh, really?
Were there a lot of customers today?
The dinner rush hit hard
when I got here, right?
- That's when our restaurant was falling apart.
- Really?
Sweetheart!
How are you?
Hey!
Are you tired?
Do you want some calamansi juice?
I'm okay.
Good job.
Thank you.
Geez.
It's like a tsunami swept through.
Wow, that drained me.
Oh yeah.
- I'm okay.
- But at least it's just physical.
We weren't stressed out.
No one's fought yet.
Someone has to fight?
- Like when you want to kill each other.
- So it's just stress.
- But...
- I think I was just stressed internally.
Because like,
I was juggling so many pots there.
Yeah.
And then later when you sleep,
you kind of like, "Okay..."
Oh my God, you know what?
When I sleep at night,
the moment I close my eyes and I dream,
I still dream about cooking.
I dream about the palabok.
I dream about the gising-gising.
It's like I'm living in a simulation.
- Who is he?
- He's Ji's friend, right?
- What's his name?
- Seo In Guk.
- Seo In Guk?
- Yeah.
So, he will work with us?
Because I was
kinda ordering him around earlier.
I said, "Since I'm going to do this,
you do this and do that."
And he's like...
Turns out he's a customer.
I thought he was here to help out.
That's why I was surprised.
"Why are you suddenly sitting down?"
Oh, take this.
- What is this?
- So...
It's alcohol. It's champagne.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Why don't you give it to Chef yourself?
- Oh, should I?
- 'Cause it's also my first day.
- Oh really?
- Oh, this place has been open since before?
- Yeah, this is...
- She's like Kumusta's boss.
- Boss?
Hi, boss.
- Hello.
- My name is In Guk.
I am Jodi. Nice to meet you.
Me too.
- This is our chef.
- Yes.
Thank you for helping us.
- What's this?
- Champagne.
- Champagne!
- Yes.
Thanks!
Thank you.
Thanks.
Oh, champagne!
Hey, can I get the bill?
Ah, the bill, the bill.
- Table number?
- Actually, he said free.
- Yeah, free for you.
- No, it's okay.
It's on me!
- No, no.
- It's on him!
In Korea, if we visit a friend at work,
we usually pay ourselves before we leave.
Then can you also pay for our dinner later?
What? I never said yes.
- Okay. Check.
- Okay.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you!
- Goodbye!
- Take care!
- You're our last customer, we're closing now.
- Really?
- Alright, flip the sign please.
- I flip it?
Yeah. Closed.
- Put it out like this.
- Oh, like this?
- Good job.
- Thanks. Yeah.
- Okay. Bye, In Guk.
- I'll call you.
- Thank you!
- No worries.
Bye!
Ah, we're closed.
- Let's go to eat.
- Yeah, let's go!
[Worked Hard?]
[Eat Harder!]
[Authentic K-BBQ]
[Here We Go!]
I think I'm hungry.
Yeah.
Since you came all the way here,
- Yes!
- I'll cook the grilled pork belly for you.
Thank you!
Hungry, hungry!
This type of grilled pork belly
is called pot lid pork belly.
Whoa, I thought it was just a lid.
- Ah, so that's how it's done.
- Yeah.
So is this the proper way
to cook grilled pork belly?
Yes, as the pork fat drips down the grill,
we cook the bean sprouts and kimchi with it.
- Ah, okay.
- That's how...
Yeah, it goes like that.
Okay, okay.
This is the first time
we eat together outside of the restaurant.
- Right.
- Not in the restaurant.
Oh, it's too bad
you guys couldn't go out for dinner.
[The Warmth of K-Hospitality]
Okay.
- Thank you.
- Yehey!
Okay.
Oh, thank you!
Feel free to eat what I placed on the side.
Okay!
[Let's Taste It!]
[Ji's Samgyup 101]
[Trying It Ji's Way]
Good.
[Pot Lid Pork Belly]
How was our day today?
Although we had so many...
- Struggles.
- Customers, struggles...
It was my first time
working with everyone today,
and even though things got a little hectic,
I'm glad we managed everything in the end.
Even if it was busy, you were still smiling.
Yeah.
So, it helps.
When you go to the kitchen, you're smiling.
We're stressing out.
You're smiling, so our stress goes down.
But whenever I give you the orders,
you never like it.
Because I'm afraid of you.
You always come with new orders.
"New order! Palabok! Kare-kare!"
Chef!
One palabok, one inasal...
Chef! One kare-kare...
- Chef!
- Yes!
- Yes?
- Chef!
- Yo.
- I'm afraid of you.
Every time you come, you come with new orders.
A lot of orders!
But I think the customers
really enjoyed the food,
so that felt great.
Yeah!
Do you think you can stay with us
until the end?
- Me?
- Yes.
- Oh sure!
- Really?
- Yeah!
- Yay!
Yeah.
Hello!
- I'm here!
- Arci!
[Yesterday's MVP Arci Joins In]
Hi!
- Hi!
- Hello!
Arci, Ji.
- Hello.
How's today?
Super busy!
So you must be all tired.
- Yeah.
- And hungry.
- Hungry.
- Wait, before that...
Before that, let's have this first.
Jell Life carb blocker.
Ah, for losing weight?
So the carbs don't get absorbed by the system.
- Can I... is that a gel?
- Yes, yes!
This is all natural.
With white kidney bean extract,
collagen, needle mushroom...
This is not medicine, by the way.
This is for beauty also.
Where's the grape?
This grilled pork belly
goes perfectly with somaek.
- Somaek?
- I'll show you.
- Soju and beer, mix!
- Beer!
- Yeah.
- Somaek.
If there's no bottle opener,
we do this in Korea.
Amazing!
Somaek is all about the ratio.
Usually when you stack the glasses like this,
you fill half with soju.
And then you fill the glass
all the way with beer.
Then you take a shot.
- Oh, it's a shot!
- Here.
Okay, I will try.
Thank you!
Thank you.
- Cheers!
- Well done, everyone!
- You say, "Tagay!"
Tagay!
Drink until we drop!
[Instant Relief!]
It's good.
One more.
- Ah, one more, okay.
- One more.
Looks like I'll be mixing shots all night!
Here.
Sorry.
Oh, thank you!
Okay. I'm a somaek preacher.
Why is it like this?
Is it one drink after another?
- Yes.
- Is it really like that?
You have to drink it like, no pacing?
That wasn't my intention.
Chef asked for one more...
Let's go!
Cheers!
- Cheers.
- This was Chef's plan all along.
It's delicious.
As if I'm drinking alcohol. I even did this.
Because that's a sign of respect for them
if you're younger.
- Okay, thank you.
- Chef, get some for me too.
What's "delicious" in Korean?
- "Masisseoyo."
- "Masisseoyo?"
"Masisseoyo."
It feels weird that we're eating.
- Yeah.
- And not serving.
I'm still working, guys.
- Oh, right.
- I keep mixing shots for you.
- Cook meat, give it to you...
- You're ordering him around!
It's all because of Chef.
You want to sit here?
Isn't it too late?
Okay, do your job.
I think we need to fix our...
- Strategy for tomorrow?
- Strategy, yeah.
So I think that we'll have to...
Let's say, designate a dispatcher
just for the orders.
- Yeah.
- Yes, because it was really hard earlier
when all the orders were coming in
and no one was there to cross everything out.
- So we don't know...
- It was very confusing.
Yeah, we're not sure what was already served.
Then I'll try to call
a few friends to help out.
How many?
- How many friends?
- Usually when you hear this,
don't you just say "thank you"?
"How many..."
- Thank you, thank you.
- Sure.
Thank you, sorry.
Do you want some more?
[And the night falls...]
[Day 4]
- Hello!
- Hi!
- Hi, Ji!
- Hello!
- Good morning.
Welcome to our kitchen again.
- It's good?
- Perfect.
You need anything? Need help?
- Okay, so we have a new dish for today.
- Okay.
- Which is sisig.
- Sisig.
[Today's Menu: Sisig]
Sisig is pork head.
Is it maskara?
- Yes. It's two ways.
- Okay.
And then so what we did is,
we have a soft part here.
[Pork Ear & Cheeks]
[Sisig]
[A sizzling, savory dish
of chopped pig's head and liver]
[seasoned with calamansi and chili]
And then we have a crunchy part.
[Deep-Fry Pork Cheeks]
We have a liver sauce.
- Is it pig's liver?
- It's pig's liver.
Okay.
[Boil Pork Liver with Spices and Seasonings]
[Blend Boiled Pork Liver]
[Liver Sauce]
Just add calamansi.
Calamansi.
Chef, what if the customers ask,
"What's sisig?"
It's pork head that we braised and fried
with liver sauce.
I want you to taste it
so that you know what you're serving.
You eat liver?
Actually, it's my first time trying it.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Okay, there's always a first time.
Here we go.
Tell me what you think, then we can adjust it.
How is it?
I think I'm just not used to the liver sauce,
but it's good.
Okay.
Alright, that's a sisig dance.
- Ji, would you like to try?
- Ah, okay.
With rice...
You, uh...
Okay. Alright.
Okay, stop looking at us so that we can focus.
There goes Chef again.
Okay?
Ji, are you ready to open?
Yes, I'm ready.
Kindly open the sign outside.
Flip over.
Sisig. Today's new menu.
Okay.
Alright.
[12:00 PM]
[Customers Enter]
Hello! Welcome.
- Table for two?
- Yes.
You can sit wherever you like.
- Here's your menu.
- Thank you.
- Let me know when you're ready.
- Alright, thank you.
I can't look at him properly.
Me too.
- Heart racing.
- Yeah.
Wow! Why is this place so nice?
- Hello!
- We're two.
- Oh, hello!
- Two?
So cute!
Let me know when you're ready.
What do you want to eat?
I don't want to eat.
Why don't you want to eat?
Let's have the chicken.
Oh, they have rice noodles.
Oh, rice noodles?
- Huh?
- Do you want it?
This isn't rice noodles.
Chicken.
Here's your welcome drink.
- It's calamansi juice.
- Thank you.
- No, I don't want it.
- You don't?
[Pouty Little VIP!]
It's all yours, Mom.
This is for Table 7, their appetizer.
- Thank you!
- Okay, thank you.
Here are your appetizers.
[UGH...]
That little girl isn't in the mood to eat.
It's like one of those moments
when you just hate everything.
Ice cream.
- Ice cream.
- Want the one with shrimp?
Ice cream, ice cream.
Let's get ice cream later.
No, I want it now.
Oh, this...
[Who's Crying...?]
Ice cream, ice cream.
Hi!
Hello. Hi!
- Say hello.
- You want ice cream?
Yes? Ice cream, yes?
- Say yes.
- Okay, okay.
Smile!
[Jodi's Mission: Make The Little VIP Smile]
Hi!
Yay!
Thank you.
Enjoy!
[Can It Make Her Smile?]
It's so yummy!
[Mmm~~]
You should make her happy.
That's Chef's job.
Making the child happy with the magic of food.
- Alright, let's go!
- Okay.
[Now It's Chef's Turn!]
Okay.
Alright, inasal.
- Palabok is ready for...
- Palabok's ready.
Table 7.
- Table 7.
- Palabok.
Alright. Here's your palabok.
Thank you.
It's rice noodles. Want to try?
Why is there spicy sauce in rice noodles?
I don't think it's spicy.
It doesn't look yummy.
[Will Chef's Magic Work on Our Little VIP?]
Try it while it's warm.
How is it?
You're soaking up all the sauce.
[Next Up: Inasal]
[WOW]
[Yum!]
[Proud Uncle]
Hi!
Is it good?
So cute!
- So cute!
- Gising-gising.
The baby is so cute! So cute!
The baby?
She was saying hi to me.
Do you miss Jude?
- You miss Jude?
- Yes.
Okay, I'm not going to
think about Jude right now.
Hello! Welcome.
Please let me know when you're ready.
- Hello! Welcome.
- Hello!
- Let me know when you're ready.
- Oh, thank you.
Palabok. One fish...
- One inasal.
- Inasal.
- Sisig.
- Okay.
Just G-Rice, Jodi.
Okay, Table 3.
One inasal, one kare-kare,
garlic rice, and Zero Coke.
For Table 1, it's one inasal,
one sisig, one kare-kare.
Ji, can I get this one please?
Thank you.
Fish and inasal.
And then, kare-kare.
One fish.
And then, inasal.
- Inasal?
- Inasal.
- Yes, for Table 4.
- Four.
- Okay, palabok is ready. This is...
- Table 7.
- Palabok.
- Okay, palabok.
Table 3, order complete!
Table 7, orders complete!
I think this is a good system.
What's happening here is working well.
Excuse me!
It's hot.
Yup, we need to have two inasals for Table 3.
Oh my gosh.
Oh my gosh. Wow!
Whoo! Free facial!
And then...
Onions.
Spring onions.
Calamansi.
Red chili.
Sisig!
Table 4 and Table 1.
- Here's your sisig.
- Thank you.
- Thank you. What is this?
It's called sisig.
- Ah, sisig.
- Yes.
- This looks good.
- Let's try it?
- It's tasty.
- Really?
It tastes like those savory innards.
It's so delicious!
This sauce is so good.
Good, right?
Hello! Welcome.
Hello.
Where would you like to sit?
- Hello! Welcome.
- Hello!
- Would you like to sit here?
- Yes.
- Here's your menu.
- Thank you.
[Certified Hotspot]
[All tables full!]
We'll be getting these.
Inasal, sea bream, and sisig.
I wasn't able to try these yesterday.
This one's a new menu for today.
[Customer From Yesterday]
Would you like to take a look at the menu?
Okay.
Is this all available?
Except for the fish.
- Ah, fish.
- We no longer have the fish.
[Sea bream sold out...]
- Why isn't the sea bream available?
- What a shame.
Well, there's nothing we can do.
[Finally It's Available!]
We'll have sinigang.
- Okay.
- Inasal, one sea bream, and one sisig.
Okay. And three San Miguel?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Okay, Table 9.
Table 6!
Alright, Table 5!
Chef, you have two fish, okay?
- Ah, two?
- Are you aware?
- Yes, two fish.
- Okay.
- Two fish.
- And the palabok, how many?
- You've got two now.
- Okay.
[Running Smoothly]
- Palabok is up.
- Okay, thank you.
Tables 5 and 6, palabok.
This is your palabok.
Here's your gising-gising.
Hello, this is your gising-gising.
Fish.
One fish up!
Okay. Table 6, Chin.
Thank you.
The fish keeps staring at me.
The fish?
Hello, this is your fish.
- Oh, it's big!
- Yes, it's big, right?
- Enjoy!
- Thank you.
- Try the fish.
- What?
Try the fish.
The fish is good, right?
Are we going home?
- Thank you.
- Here you go.
- Have a good day.
Bye!
Here's your sinigang.
Thank you.
Enjoy your meal!
This soup is sour.
Why don't you try a sip first?
I heard it's a hit or miss.
I like this kind of flavor.
- I liked it yesterday, too.
- Really?
What is this? Meat?
Yeah, meat.
This is the new dish, right?
It's good!
Yeah.
But I'm excited for the sea bream.
[His Obsession Is Real...]
[DayBREAMing About Sea DREAM]
Fish up!
Here's your sea bream.
- Enjoy!
- Thank you.
- This is amazing!
- The visuals are insane!
I know, right!
Take a good picture.
[BREAM Come True!]
Let me break this apart.
- This is insane!
- Right.
I'll put some on your plate.
Thank you.
Let me put it here.
Wow, this is so good!
- It's good.
- Yeah, it's so good.
Good!
I'm satisfied.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- I came back for the food.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
Take care!
I'll close the restaurant now!
Yay!
[03:00 PM]
- We're done!
- Yay! We will be fed!
[Closed]
[Break Time]
Ji, hangover?
Okay, I'll give you special.
- Why special?
- Wow, special only for him?
Because they're a love team.
Ay, okay.
So, you can fall in line.
Oh, there's a line?
We weren't informed, Chef.
That's favoritism, Chef!
Yeah.
He's the guy! My new brother.
Oh okay, thank you.
- New brother?
- Brother.
- We are somaek brothers!
- Make-believe brothers!
Cheers!
- One more.
- Oh, one more. Okay.
- Looks like I'll be mixing shots all night.
- Just chugging it down.
Don't worry about me. I can keep mixing these.
Okay.
Can we eat? Okay, let's eat, sit down.
Yay!
Give me five minutes.
- Five seconds!
- Five minutes, come on...
Okay.
[Preparing for Staff Meal]
We're going to make arroz caldo
for the staff meal.
Just boil this in beef stock and then...
Lemongrass if you like. And ginger!
Okay.
Shirataki!
- Put the stock?
- Yeah.
Should we chop the lemongrass?
- Just go like this.
- I don't know how to...
So the flavor comes out?
Yeah.
And then drop it.
Same with the ginger.
Ginger is always nice.
And it's also...
Especially for those who are tired.
- Right?
- Yeah.
- So it's like cooking risotto, almost.
And then... Yeah, just keep going.
Okay.
As in just the fish sauce? For flavor?
- Yeah.
- Nothing else?
Chicken powder.
It's good!
[Adding Some K-Flavor]
Kimchi here.
Then, this is the topping.
[K-Arroz Caldo Complete!]
- Okay.
- Wow!
- What's for lunch?
Okay, this is...
What's this? Wow!
- It's for you.
- Shirataki rice!
Shirataki?
Porridge.
- Okay.
- Let's eat!
I wonder what it tastes like.
This is good!
Ji?
Shirataki rice is...
Like, it has zero carbs.
Do Filipinos eat this porridge a lot?
When you're hungover.
When you're sick...
Or when you're sick.
I cooked this because I remember yesterday...
You cooked kimchi...
So I make, yeah.
So Filipino and Korean flavors are combined.
So it's a fusion food.
It's good.
So good!
The porridge is so good.
- Good.
I think the lunch service today
went much smoother than yesterday.
I personally think
the discussion we had yesterday
about our strategy for today worked.
That's why everything was seamless
during the lunch service.
- It's a bit warm from the cue.
- They're cold.
- What?
You're cold?
But it was colder when we first got here.
- Yeah.
- Five days ago.
Oh, really?
It's like the temperature suddenly dropped.
And all of a sudden, it became so cold.
This is when the weather is nicest in Korea.
- Now?
- Yes.
Right now.
Yeah.
[As of Filming]
[Fall in Korea]
[About 16~20°C]
[Perfect Weather for Koreans]
[Nice Saturday Evening]
[How chaotic will it be tonight?]
Here comes the night again.
Kumusta!
Let's go! Good luck!
We're going to do good today!
I have a great feeling! Yeah.
Okay, I'm making my own station here.
- Let's do the sisig here.
- Okay.
I'll put the sisig here.
And then, I'll put the sizzling plates.
These all go at the bottom, right?
- Yes.
- Okay, so I'm doing it right.
Yes, everything.
We're good with the calamansi, Chef.
- What else?
- Thank you.
Your liver sauce is here.
Garlic chips.
You don't need this anymore,
so I'll clean this up.
Thank you. You're the best.
Thank you, Ji.
[Kumusta Members Busy Preparing]
Oh, here it is!
I guess we just go in.
[Two Mysterious Men Entering The Restaurant]
Oh, it's nice!
Wow, why is this place so nice?
- What?
- I'm surprised!
Oh my, oh my.
Oh my, our staff.
If we are lucky tomorrow,
if we have more hands
or more people coming in to help us...
- Oh well, we have one plus one.
- Yes.
I'll try calling one or two people.
Oh, that will be perfect.
[Kim Myung Soo - Singer & Actor]
Hello!
- Hello!
[Kim Min Seok - Actor]
Hi, baby.
Where are you?
I'm in Korea, remember?
Look at Mama's uniform!
- What does it say?
- Mama's uniform.
Kumusta!
Mama, are you a chef?
Yeah, I'm a chef right now.
I'm cooking a lot of food.
You want palabok?
Yes, are you going to cook palabok there?
Yeah, I cook a lot of palabok.
- Jude, Jude, Jude!
- Yes.
- You miss Mama?
Yes.
How much do you miss Mama?
A lot!
A lot?
Me too, I miss you so much.
Three sleeps!
Three more sleeps.
You sleep three more times
and then Mama will be home.
- Okay?
- Okay!
I love you!
Okay, thank you.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye.
Okay.
What a day...